One act of kindness lives on forever.
White Bird is a drama, war film directed by Marc Forster.
After being expelled from Beecher Prep for his treatment of a classmate with a
facial deformity, Julian has struggled to fit in at his new school.
To transform his life, Julian's grandmother finally reveals her own story of courage of her
youth in Nazi-occupied France, where a classmate shelters her from mortal danger.
Sara (Young Grandmére), played by Ariella Glaser.
Julien Beaumier, played by Orlando Schwerdt.
Julian Albans, played by Bryce Gheisar.
Vivienne Beaumier, played by Gillian Anderson.
Grandmére, played by Helen Mirren.
Jean-Paul Beaumier, played by Jo Stone-Fewings.
White Bird (marketed with the subtitle A Wonder Story) is a 2024 American war drama film directed by Marc
Forster from a screenplay by Mark Bomback, based on the 2019 graphic novel of the same name by R.
Serving as both a spin-off prequel and a sequel to Wonder (2017), it stars Ariella Glaser, Orlando Schwerdt, Bryce
Gheisar, Gillian Anderson, and Helen Mirren, with Gheisar reprising his role as Julian Albans from Wonder.
White Bird was released in Italy, Slovenia, and Croatia on January 4, 2024; it was released in the
United States by Lionsgate on October 4, 2024, to positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of france, nazi, holocaust
(shoah), world war ii, private school.
The tone is emotional.